Guide to the Komen Foundation, Houston Records
University of Houston Libraries
- Mulitmedia, id74712
  - Video, id143011
    - “The Power of a Promise”, undated; id143050 (Ovs box 35, Item 21)
    - “The Power of a Promise”, undated; id143051 (Ovs box 35, Item 22)
    - “For the Cure”, undated; id143052 (Ovs box 35, Item 23)
    - “Celebrate”, undated; id143053 (Ovs box 35, Item 24)
    - Debra Duncan Show, undated; id143054 (Ovs box 35, Item 25)
    - BMW Driven to Find A Cure, undated; id143055 (Ovs box 35, Item 26)
    - Unknown, undated; id143056 (Ovs box 35, Item 27)
- Unprocessed Materials, id164381
  Scope and Contents
  The Komen Foundation donated approximately 7 linear feet of additional materails to UH Libraries in 2015. These are curently unprocessed and not yet available for research.
  - Kroger posters, id172889 (File cabinet F, Drawer 9, Ovs folder 1)
- Komen Foundation, Houston Records 2016 Accession, id176091
  Additional unprocessed materials acquired April 28, 2016